originaltrilogy.com 2012-06-13

# Privacy Policy - originaltrilogy.com

This Policy applies to all of the products, services and web sites offered by TEH Innernets, LLC or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies (collectively, TEH Innernets' "services"). 

**IP Address, Browser Statistics, Geographical Location, etc.**   
While you browse the site, our web servers collect information that is not personally identifiable, including your IP address, the web browser you use, and your geographical location. We may use this information for research and marketing purposes. For example, we might use your geographical location to serve banners ads that are more relevant to your market. This information may be provided to third parties in order to implement these research and marketing programs. 

**Account Sign Up Information**   
When you create an account with us, we request your e-mail address in order to provide login credentials. This e-mail address will only be used for administrative purposes; it will never be sold to an e-mail list or made public without your consent. At the time of account creation, if you opt in to our newsletter, your e-mail address will be added to our mailing list and used solely for the purpose of sending our newsletter. 

**Purchasing Information**   
Any information you submit for paid services from us will be used solely for fulfilling those services (payment processing, shipping, etc.). 

**Browser Cookies**   
We make use of cookies to track user access, including site login. You may adjust your web browser's settings to block cookies entirely or warn you whenever a web site attempts to deposit a cookie on your computer. Please note that disabling cookies will prevent you from accessing certain originaltrilogy.com features and services. 

**User Communications**   
When you send email or other communication to originaltrilogy.com, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

**Affiliated Sites**   
We offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to TEH Innernets in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. 

**Link Tracking**   
We may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the effectiveness of our advertising. 

**Other Web Sites**   
This Privacy Policy applies to web sites and services that are owned and operated by TEH Innernets. We do not exercise control over other web sites we may link to from our services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. 

**Choices for Personal Information**   
When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. 

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent. 

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case TEH Innernets may not be able to provide those services to you. 

**Information Sharing**   
TEH Innernets only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of our network of sites in the following limited circumstances: 

\- We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.   
\- We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.   
\- We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of TEH Innernets, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. 

If TEH Innernets becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Such information does not identify you individually. 

Please contact us at the address below for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data. 

**Information Security**   
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

We restrict access to personal information to TEH Innernets employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

**Data Integrity**   
TEH Innernets processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

**Accessing and Updating Personal Information**   
When you use our services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Some of our services have different procedures to access, correct or delete users' personal information. We provide the details for these procedures in the specific privacy notices or FAQs for these services. 

**Enforcement**   
TEH Innernets regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or TEH Innernets' treatment of personal information by contacting us through our contact form. 

**Changes to This Policy**   
Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes). Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review. 

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through our contact form.
